当我谈到 DMSO 如何帮助
when I talk about how d m s O has helped
我改善疤痕组织的血流时
me get blood flow in my scar tissue
我指的就是这个
this is what I'm talking about
这是我的脚背
this is the top of my foot here
这是我的小腿下部
this is the lower part of my leg
疤痕沿着这里向上延伸
the scarring goes up along here
然后一直向下蔓延到这里
and then all down in here
你大概能看到这里颜色有点发褐
and you can kind of see how it's kind of brown
在这部分，我其实停止了在小腿上
in here  I actually quit putting d m s O on my lower
涂抹 DMSO，好让它重新变回褐色
leg so that it would turn brown again
这样你们就能明白我在说什么了
so you can see what I'm talking about  so
十年前
I was in a bad wreck
我遭遇了一场严重的车祸
ten years ago
大约是十多年前
little over 10 years ago
我腿上的这个部位当时伤得很
this part of my leg was pretty
几乎完全被压碎了
much completely crushed
为我做手术的医生们保住了我的腿
and the doctors who operated on me saved my leg
我对此深表感激
I'm very thankful for that
他们从我的脚背取了很多结缔组织
they took a lot of the connective tissue from the top
翻转过来并用在了这里
of my foot and turned it around and used it in here
我做了多次植皮手术，那是
I had multiple skin grafts and that's
你能看出来植皮留下的痕迹
you can tell the skin grafts leave
就在这里，留下了这种奇奇怪怪的皮肤
this kind of funky skin right here
然后我还有这些地方
and then I've got these places
皮肤没有完全长好
where the skin didn't quite
并没有完全长成他们想要的样子
grow back quite like what they wanted
但这确实是一个非常困难的
but this was a really difficult
部位，让他们很难
place for them to get it to
真正重新生长出来
actually grow back
因为这里的血液循环
because the just this blood
血液循环就是不通畅
flow was just not happening
在我开始使用 DMSO 之前
before I started using the DMSO
我尝试过很多不同的方法来改善
I tried lots of different things to help with
血液循环，有些方法确实起了一点作用
the circulation and some things worked some
但效果并不理想
but not great
你可以看到这里有点发褐，看起来脏兮兮的
where you can see it's kind of brown and yucky here
这以前其实一直蔓延到我的整个脚部
this was actually all the way down throughout my foot
沿着我脚背上的这道疤痕一直延伸过去
all the way across this scar on the top of my foot
然后是这一块区域，你可以看到
and then this area which you can see
挺明显的，看起来又褐又灰的
pretty well  it's pretty brown and gray looking
在我开始使用 DMSO 之前
it had it had actually turned pretty much
它实际上已经几乎完全变成了灰色
completely gray before I started using the DMSO
然后看下面这一块区域
and then this area down here see
看到它是那种很深的紫色了吗
how it's real purpley that
那里一直保持着深紫色
that just stayed dark purple
呈现出棕色和灰色
and brown and gray looking
看起来很恶心
it was it was gross
血流不畅的问题已经
the blood flow issue has been
持续了 10 年，我需要
ongoing for the last 10 years  I needed
让这里的血液循环起来
to get the blood flowing in this in this
瘢痕组织一直存在，所以
scar tissue consistently and well  that's
我就在想，好吧，我得试试
why I thought well I'll try the
DMSO（二甲基亚砜），看看会发生什么
DMSO and see what happens
这些是我在每天使用 DMSO
these are photos I took 2 weeks after
和芦荟混合物两周后拍摄的照片
using the DMSO and aloe Vera mix daily
你可以看到这确实增加了
you can see that it really increased the
流向那个疤痕区域的血流量
blood flow into that scarred area
还发生了另一件让我非常惊讶的事情
something else happened that really surprised me
这里的大部分区域一直处于麻木状态
most of this has been numb
表面和皮下都完全没有知觉
completely numb on the surface and underneath
我这上面有感觉了
I have feeling up in here
我的脚趾有感觉了
I have feeling on my toes
我有感觉了
I have feeling
因为他们用了那些神经
because they use those nerves
从这里取出来，替换到了这里
here and replace them here
我有感觉了
I have feeling
如果我用手指划过这里的伤疤
if I run my finger across the scar here
我能感觉到那种触感传到了那边的脚趾尖上
I can feel it across the tops of my toes over there
这种感觉非常奇怪
it's very strange feeling
但确实有感觉
but it's there
在我使用了几天二甲基亚砜（DMSO）之后
so after I was using the DMSO for several days
我出去散步，然后我
I went for a walk and I
意识到我能感觉到我的脚踝了
realized I could feel my ankle
走路时我能感觉到脚踝承受的压力
I could feel the pressure on my ankle as I walked
这是在那之前我一直没有感觉到的
which is something I hadn't felt in at that point
九年半了
nine and a half years
我当时想，这真奇怪
I thought well that's odd
然后当我回到家
and then when I got home
我开始用手指抚摸那些疤痕
I started running my fingers over the scarring
我意识到我的知觉恢复了很多
and I realized I could feel a lot more
就像这整个区域已经很久没有知觉了
like this whole area hasn't had feeling
整整九年半的时间
nine and a half years
现在我用手指划过这里，能感觉到它了
and I can now run my fingers across this and feel it
现在我可以用手指划过
I can now run my fingers across
我的脚部并感觉到它，我依然能
my foot here and feel it  I still
这里大部分地方还是麻木的
a lot of this is still numb
这里开始有感觉了
this is starting to get feeling
这真的很令人惊讶
which is really surprising
考虑到那里曾经受过那么严重的伤
considering all the damage that was there
在这块疤痕组织的边缘我有感觉了
I have feeling on the edges of this scar tissue
这些感觉已经消失了九年半了，所以
that haven't been there in nine and a/2 years  so
我对此感到非常惊讶和欣慰
I'm really surprised and pleased about that